As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices We take in the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are in between the sea
and the sky Ready now for adventure We're
itching to try Get ready to roam So all
aboard now we're said to go Set sail to
the ocean so deep Ready for a truly grand
adventure Well don't you think that sounds
really fun All this
excitement second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Straw Hat, you're amazing.
You mean whores.
Come on, pull it together. Luffy.
Can you hear me?
Say something I think all those shadows
we gave him were too much after all.
Even someone as powerful as
him still isn't invincible.
He absorbed the strength
of a hundred shadows.
He pushed his body to the absolute limit.
Unless we want all this to be for nothing,
we gotta get those shadows back right now.
He's right, we gotta hurry.
Take a look to the east and
see how bad it is yourself.
The sun will be up soon.
So what now?
What do we have to do
to get the shadows back?
He took four of them from our crew!
We had a plan, but there's a little snag.
Straw Hat was the one who was
gonna make Moria give them back.
I don't think he can move in his condition,
much less make anybody do anything.
Moria took the shadows and
placed them into zombies.
As the Lord of the Shadows,
he and he alone must order them
to return to their former masters.
Otherwise, they'll stay
right where they are.
Less talk, more action! Right.
We gotta force Maurya to give the
order to release them no matter what.
If we don't get the Shadows
back, beating it was pointless.
This is bad.
Horses back on his feet.
That's impossible how the Hennessy ate
him to move after beating you like that.
That's it!
We're done for!
Most of the Straw Hats
are down for the count!
They were our last hope!
And the Shadows!
We already used them against
them and it wasn't enough!
That was the best shot we had!
Even if the Straw Hats could
fight, he's too strong!
That didn't hurt at all!
Damn you!
He really is a demon!
There's no way we can win!
We're completely out of options.
We never stood a chance.
We'll be stuck living in
this darkness forever.
Forever!
We gotta retreat.
If we stay here, we're all gonna die.
Yeah, let's head back to the
forest where the sun never shines.
Back to the night forever.
I don't believe it!
I'm not sure how it was for Luffy,
but oars took one hell of a beating.
Whoa, hold on.
You need to take it easy.
You don't want to die, do you?
After oars pounded him
mercilessly, he can still stand?
How could that be?
Is he some kind of zombie too?
What?
What happened to the bodies
of the Straw Hat crew?
They were right here.
Where'd they go? What the?
Hey, you're right.
They were here just a second ago.
They're unconscious.
They can't move around on their own.
What happened to these two?
Huh? They're gone.
That long-nosed guy and
the woman just disappeared.
They couldn't have gotten up and
run away on their own, could they?
How could they all
disappear at the same time?
Oh, we can't worry about it now.
We gotta run.
I'd love to give him just one
more punch. Straw Hat? You two?
What are you guys made of?
But I can't move, damn it!
My body's too worn out
to get up right now!
Robin!
Yes, I'm right here.
Hey!
They didn't run away!
I want to get up there! I understand.
I'll provide some footholds for you.
I, too, am still willing and able to help.
A living, breathing, talking
skeleton with an apro!
No way! Good to hear.
I've already got a plan.
Just as I thought.
Everybody's back up and
ready for the next round.
She's back.
And how did she get up there?
Wait,
you mean these guys didn't
even think about running
away from the second the
door stood back up again?
They were all just getting
ready for the next round!
Just wait
Chopper we gotta hurry
the sun's coming up Right
Do you think we can still use
this thing It's fine come on
I don't believe it And
to think we were all
about to throw in the towel Hey it's about
to get real ugly here
so get out of the way
Okay gotcha we'll leave
it to you then Now,
pierre la fleur.
Here we go. Let's do it.
Hey, come back.
The heck is this stuff?
Some smoke? Clouds?
The forecast calls for rain.
Cool ball!
Rain tip-up!
Where'd that rain come from?
Yeah, see some kind of
wizard or something?
All right, emergency plumbing
construction complete!
Cut it out!
Now, coo tip-up!
What the?
Come on, Usa!
Give it all you got!
I am!
If you want to freeze a giant, nothing
means a super-sized Sub-Zero wing cannon.
Now, fire!
I'm frozen!
I can't move!
Awesome!
They've frozen with the rainwater!
Now it's my turn!
What the...
Suck on this!
Stupid change! You did it!
Get that thing off me!
Nice! Good shot!
Now toss me!
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I'm sure I'll be fine!
My body's made of rubber!
Take care!
Time for third gear!
Boom balloon!
Zoro, your turn!
Go for the stomach!
Leave it to me!
Three-sword style!
Ultimate attack!
Three thousand worlds!
My turn again! Take this!
Good one, Sanji!
We got his back nice and straight now!
What in the hell are these guys doing?
The structure's the same as a human's,
which means the spine is S-shaped,
designed to carry weight as well
as soften impact to the body.
But when the spine is
pulled into a straight line,
it won't be able to absorb impact,
and he'll have to bear the
full force of Luffy's attack.
Do it!
Best of luck!
Get ready for a special bazooka!
Huh?
So what?
I'll just knock you back
with my own special bazooka!
Kum Kum!
My arm's being all crappy!
I can't stretch!
His inability to feel any pain
turned out to be a weakness.
Time to finish him off
and take back your shadow.
Now, Kum Kum!
Yeah! Yeah! Take it, Luffy!
Take it down, Straw Hat!
Do it!
Here's my giant...
...Bazooka!
He did it!
I don't care if you're a zombie.
No one could get back up
after something like that.
He lost.
He really lost.
Even though he was so big.
What's going to happen to Thriller Bark?
They really did it.
I knew they could.
That Straw Hat crew is something else.
It seems like I invited nothing
but trouble to the island.
What happened to our master?
Can anybody see him?
They did it!
They really did it this time!
Ha ha!
Thank you so much!
You guys are the best!
They really were our
shining stars of hope!
I told you, Straw Hat is our savior!
Let's hear it for...
What the hell?
I don't understand.
Why'd you get so tiny?
It doesn't hurt, but I can't move.
He's still conscious.
Even with his bones crushed, he can't die.
These zombies really do
make a mockery of life.
The sun's coming up.
What is this?
This strange sensation
coursing through my bones.
Hey, Luffy!
Hurry up with those shadows,
the sun is coming up!
What are you cheering about?
Unless you get your shadows back,
you're all going to burn to ashes!
Wow, you're right! I forgot.
We gotta hurry.
All right, then.
Let's go wake Mordial with the beating
and make him release the shadows.
Morning's almost here.
No need.
I'm awake.
Hey!
Master's alive!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Of course, I wasn't
worried about him at all.
Fine, that just saves us the
trouble of waking you ourselves.
Now,
unless you want another serious beating
from the Straw Hats, you'll do what we say.
Give the order!
Return all the shadows now!
Yeah, give them back, you bastard!
What do you think this
is, a playground brawl?
A true pirate would never
bow to demands like that,
not even if his life depended on it.
Saw you teamed up with those
losers from the forest, did you?
What a joke Now I see how Straw Hat
got that ridiculous increase in power?
How desperate you must be to use
my own shadow abilities against me!
You shut your mouth!
Return the shadows at once!
Straw Hat Luffy, you've got some
nerve making a mess of Thriller Bark!
You'll pay for what you've
done to my glorious ship!
You're the one who's gonna pay!
It's your fault for picking
a fight with my crew!
Now get back those shadows
before the sun comes up!
Why, when at this point all I have to do
is sit around and wait for you all to die?
I'm afraid you're not cut
out for the new world, kid.
I admit you've got some good
underlings, but it doesn't matter.
All will be lost.
And do you know why?
Why?
Straw Hat, this isn't exactly the
time to sit around and chit-chat.
Take a look at the sky.
It's getting brighter.
Focus on getting the shadows back.
We're almost out of time!
Because unlike me, you've yet to
realize the weakness of your crew.
They were mortal!
That's what makes things
different this time.
Had they been zombies from the beginning,
I would have had nothing to lose.
Zomnius are fearless,
eternal, relentless warriors that can
be replaced even if they fall! Now,
with my army of the undead,
there's nothing in the world that will
stop me from becoming king of the pirates!
You and your crew should be grateful
for the chance to serve as my slaves!
Miss! It's not me!
Now, every last shot of Ibrillabark,
come to me and become my power!
SHADOWS! ASCARD!
What's happening?
His shadow came out!
Are these shadows?
No way!
He's gathering up every shadow on this
island and pumping them into his body!
Tell me, Straw Hat Luffy,
from your strength I'd say you
absorbed about a hundred shadows,
right?
Then I shall take one
hundred, two hundred,
three hundred,
four hundred,
five hundred,
We're screwed!
It's all over.
We can't even hide from that thing. Nice.
Back to normal.
The sun is rising.
It's almost done.
We're out of time.
Straw Hat needed a
hundred shadows to take.
There's no way we can defeat him.
Not even with devil
fruit powers on our side.
Face it, we're all doomed
What's the point of even trying?
He'll beat us no matter what we do
He's got Straw Hats shadow inside him too
Oh, no!
He's wrecking his own ship!
We gotta get out of here right now!
Run!
Run to the forest!
We're never gonna make it!
There's no way, man!
I'm on fire!
My skin's melting!
Somebody help! Get up!
Run for the forest!
The sun is coming up!
We can't fight anymore.
All we can do is run and hide.
Captain Lola!
Hey, come on, Captain!
Why are you just standing there like that?
Hurry up!
You guys can run if you want.
What the hell are you saying?
The sun will kill you too, you know.
I have to take some
responsibility this battle
it's my fight too look at them do you see?
They're not budging they're
completely fearless!
They're in the same
boat we are they've lost
their shadows too come on you don't
think they? can still win. Yeah, really.
They're goners if the sun hits them,
and look at Merde, he's indestructible.
He's even stronger than Orbs.
If they won't give up on this fight,
then I'm with them all the way.
I thought our battle
might end up like this,
but I was willing to place my bets
on the Straw Hats all the same,
and I don't regret making
that decision one single bit.
There's no way we could defeat that thing.
Then go ahead and run.
It's my job to see this through.
I'm your captain.
And as your leader, I want you to be safe.
Captain Lola! Hurry!
You're in the sunlight!
You gotta get in the shadows, quick!
I'm fine where I am!
This is what it means to
put your faith in someone!
And I won't falter!
Don't do it, Captain!
You can't!
You're gonna get killed!
I accept whatever fate
has in store for me.
Live or die, that's my final decision!
Here is where I stand.
I'm never leaving the light again
No, Captain
This guy is the big boss, right?
Because I don't think
they get much bigger He
let his pride and anger
get the best of him,
and now he's losing control of himself.
All right, you guys,
we're almost out of time!
I'm gonna have to go wild here.
It's up to you to take care of
the rest You got it, Captain!
Take him down, Luffy!
What's with you guys?
Are you out of your damn minds?
There's no way we can win here!
He's a monster with the
strength of a thousand people!
Exactly!
Think for a minute!
He's got your shadows
trapped in there, too!
Which means he's got your powers!
On top of that, you've
only got a few minutes!
Shut your mouth if you're
not gonna help us out!
This battle's already over,
and Moria knows he's lost. Huh?
Our real enemy here is the sun.
In other words, it's a
fight against the clock.
Moria sucking in all
those shadows was just
a desperate move to try and buy some time.
All right, second gear!
Either the sun wipes us out or
Moria destroys himself. Go, Luffy!
Take him down!
You see that?
The shadows are escaping!
It looks like hundreds of
shadows are pouring out!
How can they get out?
I thought the shadows
were under his command.
Merde is losing consciousness, so he's
losing control of the shadows he stole, too!
Not even he's powerful enough for his
mind to handle that many shadows at once!
Gum-Gum! No! Break that!
I call that one the black box!
Damn it, he trapped me!
I'll crush him!
Direct hit.
From the fist that cracked the island.
Straw Hat, no!
Don't do it!
Consider this your punishment!
Now you know what happens
to cocky little snorts
that think they can sail
into my neck of the sea.
This is the fate of all those who
stand in the way of the seven warlords.
You gotta know your
place in the world, kid.
Nails that stick out.
They're only asking to
get hammered back in.
Luffy! Stop it!
A nail that sticks out.
But I'll tell you this.
No one will ever?
Hammer me down!
You really believe that, don't you?
It's almost impressive
how damn arrogant you are,
kid What the hell makes you
think you're so indestructible?
As rubber bounces back.
Mark my words!
I'm going to make you spit
out all those shadows!
Is this guy for real?
He might do it!
Don't jinx it!
The sun's coming up!
Laura, get back in the shade or
you're going to disintegrate!
Help me!
I'm on fire! Pull back!
We're running out of places to hide here!
Third gear!
He's gonna bump it up to third gear what
is he out of his mind you've got to stop!
Movie you're going way too far don't you
remember what happened the
last time you use that?
Oh, come!
Giant!
Shack!
Holy crap!
He's leaking shadows!
I'm dying anywhere.
I'm in control here.
Listen to me, Shadows.
I am your master and you will obey me.
Now get back in there!
That evil bastard!
He's fighting them all back!
They can't get out!
Can you hear me, my shadow?
Come back right now!
I'm waiting for you!
Now return to me!
We've been together ever since birth!
We were born as one!
You don't belong to him!
We belong together!
Please return to me!
I've spent three long years searching
for the zombie you were trapped inside!
And now you're right in front of me!
If you can hear my voice, please return!
Come back to me!
Gabiola!
We can't let you stand out
here and destroy yourself!
Get in the shade before it's too late!
Come on, don't tell me
you guys can't feel it!
They're right there!
She's right.
He's got our shadows.
Every one of them is
inside Morty's stomach.
Not even a hundred feet from us.
If we run, we might
never get another chance.
Still, we can't take on a warlord.
We've got to try. Come back!
Come back to us!
Return home, shadows!
Come back, shadows!
You know what?
I've got some words for my shadow, too!
If you really want to be the shadow
of the King of the Pirates...
...then you better shape up!
And come back, now!
I don't know.
Straw Hat you bastard!
Just you watch!
You think you had it tough so far?
You don't even know tough!
But don't worry, the real nightmare's
waiting for you in the new world!
They're coming back!
They're actually coming back!
Hey!
Quick, get down, you guys!
Shadow!
Hurry back to me!
What's going on?
Little baby!